brokebackasians.com 2018-05-11

# BrokeBackAsians.com - Privacy Policy

**OUR COMMITMENT TO PRIVACY**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on BrokeBackAsians.com and all websites in the network.

**WHAT DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION FOR?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs).  
To improve our websites (we continually strive to improve our websites offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you).  
To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs).  
To process transactions. Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.  
To send periodic emails. The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

**HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

**DO WE USE COOKIES?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to yur computer`s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to help compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

**DO WE DISCLOSE ANY INFORMATION TO OUTSIDE PARTIES?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**THIRD PARTY LINKS**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY ONLY**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**YOUR CONSENT**

By using our site, you consent to our on-line privacy policy.

**CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us.
